可以给我看漫画版吗
Can I see the comics?
这是"纽约时报"耶
This is the New York Times.
好 请问我可以看漫画版吗
Okay, may I see the comics?
你们不是要带罗斯去看比赛吗
I thought you were taking Ross to the game.
是啊 他会来这里跟我们碰头
We are. He's meeting us here.
不会吧 瑞秋跟我们约在这里
No, Rachel's meeting us here.
别这样 他们可以在同一个地方出现吧
Come on. They can be in the same room.
- 你真的该看看昨晚的情况   - 怎么了
- You should've been there last night.     - What happened?
罗斯去我们的公寓
Ross was hanging out at our place.
瑞秋过来跟钱德借润肤霜…
Rachel comes to borrow moisturizer from Chandler...
你不能就只是说 来借某样东西吗
How hard is it to say "something"?
瑞秋过来借…某样东西
Rachel came over to borrow "something."
反正呢 她跟罗斯就开始对彼此大吼
Anyway, her and Ross just started yelling at each other.
为什么他会对她吼 是他跟别人上床耶
Why was he yelling at her? He slept with someone else.
因为他说当时他们两人是暂时分开的状态
He says they were on a break when it happened...
所以她早该原谅他了
...so she should've forgiven him by now.
他太不讲理了吧 天啊
He is so unreasonable. God.
不过我想我懂他的意思
Although I understand what he means.
天啊 这好像在看"六十分钟"
Oh, my God. This is like 60 Minutes...
一开始你很气制药公司
...when at first you're mad at that pharmaceutical company...
制造药品
...for making the drug.
然后你又为大众感到难过…
And then, you just feel bad for the people because...
因为他们想要生出头发
...they needed to make their hair grow.
这超像我父母离婚的时候
You know, this is like when my parents got divorced.
天啊 我希望罗斯不会在童子军活动结束后绑架我
I hope Ross doesn't try to kidnap me after Cub Scouts.
我梦到罗斯和瑞秋两人还在一起 从没分手
I dreamed that Ross and Rachel were still together.
大家都聚在一起 很开心
And we were all hanging out and happy.
我做了同样的梦
I had the same dream.
- 而且没人跟那个影印女孩上床 - 噢 我梦到的刚好相反
- And nobody slept with the Xerox girl.     - Oh, I had the opposite dream.
或许之后就会没事 已经过一个礼拜了
Maybe it's gonna be okay. I mean, it's been a week.
我从来不会花超过一个礼拜的时间为爱伤神
It never takes me more than a week to get over a relationship.
你洗个澡就不再为爱伤神了
It never takes you more than a shower to get over a relationship.
好 我们走吧 准备去看今晚的精彩表演
Let's go. Let's hit the road. Let's get the show on it.
先让我买杯咖啡
Let me get coffee.
我知道一⁮间很棒的咖啡厅 离这里很近
I know the best coffeehouse. And it's close.
比这里还近
Closer than here?
噢 你看 我找到咖啡了
Oh, look. I found coffee.
我们快走吧
Okay, let's skedaddle.
拜托 我才不要喝别人喝过的咖啡
I'm not gonna drink somebody's old coffee.
是的 女王
Okay, Your Highness.
"瑞秋 我真的很抱歉" "没关系 罗斯 你想复合吗"
"Rachel, I'm really sorry." "Okay, Ross. Wanna get back together?"
"好啊"
"Yeah, okay."
有人听到了吗
Did anyone else hear that?
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 他在这里吗   - 不在
- Is he here?     - No.
还给你的润肤霜
Here's your moisturizer.
你们一定会爱死我的 听好了
You guys are gonna love me. Okay, check it out.
我有五张星期四的票
Thursday night, five tickets.
去看卡文•克莱的睡衣秀 你们都会跟我去
Calvin Klein lingerie show, and you guys are coming with me.
我有说出来 对吧
I said that out loud, right?
对 只是我们已经…
Yes, it's just that we kind of already...
有计划了 是跟罗斯
...made plans with Ross.
嗯…好吧
Oh. Well, okay.
那好吧
Well, there you go.
他有个全新的家庭剧院设备
It's just, he got this new home-theater dealy...
他希望我们过去看看
...and he wants us to check it out.
他很兴奋
He's excited about it too.
甚至还把节目表录在答录机上面
He even recorded showtimes on his answering machine.
- 对不起   - 噢 没关系
- We're sorry, honey.     - Oh, it's okay.
瑞秋 真的不是我们不想去
Rach, it's not that we don't want to. Really.
会有穿着内衣的模特儿吗
Are we talking models in their underwear?
跟高跟鞋
And heels.
罗斯先问我们的 我们已经约好了
Ross did ask us first, and we set that night aside.
没关系 是他先问的 这没什么
Come on. If he asked you first, it's only fair.
天啊 我感觉好糟
Oh, boy, do I feel bad.
非常糟
Very bad.
钱德 你在干嘛
- Chandler, what are you doing?     - Chandler.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你又开始抽烟了
You're smoking again?
其实我是昨天开始抽烟
Well, actually, yesterday I was smoking again.
到今天还在抽
Today I'm smoking, still.
你那么辛苦的戒烟 怎么又开始抽
Why would you start again after chewing all that quitting gum?
说真的 这跟我父母的离婚一样…
This is just like my parents' divorce...
那也是我开始抽烟的时候
...which is when I first started smoking.
你那时不是只有九岁吗
Weren't you 9?
是啊
Yeah.
午睡后的第一支烟真的是…
I'm telling you something, that first smoke after naptime...
太好了 我这么倒霉 一定是他
That's great. With my luck, that's him.
他罗斯吗
Him? Ross?
不是 是赞美诗253篇 "爱的恩泽"
No, "Hymn" 253: "His Eyes Are on the Sparrow."
我父母离婚后 我开始用幽默作为我的防御机制
When my parents got divorced, I started using humor as a defense mechanism.
嗨 你们这个周末有计划吗
Hi. Uh, do you guys have weekend plans?
因为我妹说我们这个周末可以去她的小屋 然后去滑雪
Because my sister says we can spend the weekend at her cabin, skiing.
我先问了你们 对吧 我有遵守规则
I'm asking you first, right? I'm playing by the rules.
绝对有
Absolutely.
钱德 你在抽烟 你在干嘛啊
Chandler. You're smoking? What are you doing?
闭嘴 你又不是我真的妈妈
Shut up. You're not my real mom.
钱德 你可以把窗户关起来吗 我的奶头硬到可以切玻璃了
Could you close that window? My nipples could cut glass.
真的吗 我的让我躲掉罚单
Really? Because mine get me out of tickets.
我真的很感激各位花时间陪我
Look, I just wanna say I really appreciate you spending time with me.
这段时间还蛮难熬的 我只想说声谢谢
It's been a hard time right now, so I just want to say thanks.
可以找个人抱抱他吗 我得留在窗户旁边
Somebody else hug him. I have to stay by the window.
不然这个周末来个影碟马拉松 怎么样
How about this weekend, we have a laser-disc marathon, okay?
或者来个比赛 我有新的…
And maybe a tournament on my new...
飞镖靶 你们觉得怎样
...dart board. What do you think?
玩两天的飞镖 一定很棒
Two days of darts. It'll be great.
下礼拜玩一定很棒
It'll be great for next weekend.
不 不 不 这个礼拜
This weekend, guys.
下礼拜玩一定很棒
It'll be great for next weekend.
我是说 真的很棒喔
I mean, "lt'll be great."
怎么了
What's going on?
我们受邀去滑雪 去瑞秋妹妹的小屋
We're, um, sort of invited to go skiing. You know, Rachel's sister's cabin?
要去整个周末
So, for the whole weekend?
真的很抱歉 不过是她先问的
We're really sorry, but she did ask us first.
没关系 我失恋的第一个周末…
That's okay. If you all have to go away...
你们都要出城去…
...for the first weekend I'm alone by myself...
我完全可以理解
...then I totally understand.
我可以留下来 我留下来
I can stay. I'm gonna stay.
我上次去滑雪时 根本不敢跳下吊车
The last time I went, I was afraid to leave the chair lift.
就这样坐来坐去
I just went round and round.
菲比 你需要开你奶奶的车载大家去
We need you to drive us there in your grandmother's cab.
- 但是我会留下来   - 不 我留下来 他是我哥耶
- But you know what? I'll stay.     - No, I'll stay. He's my brother.
- 干嘛 同情我吗   - 没有
- What, a "pity stay"?     - No.
我们会玩得很开心的
We're gonna have fun.
我们可以做牛奶软糖
We can make fudge.
同情食物
Pity food?
没关系 我不需要你们任何人留下来
You know what? I don't need any of you to stay.
没有人该留下来
Nobody stays.
嗯 那么我也表示一下好了
Well, then I might as well offer to stay.
有人替罗斯难过吗
Does anybody else feel bad about Ross?
你觉得他还在生我们的气吗
You think he's still mad?
他可能更生气了 因为你今天早上还跟他借雪镜
He's probably more mad since you called him to borrow his goggles.
怎样 我的没有反光层啊
What? Mine aren't tinted.
钱德
Chandler.
干嘛
What?
标志上写什么
What does the sign say?
"照耀我 耶稣"
"Beam me up, Jesus."
是"禁止吸烟"那个标志
The "No Smoking" sign.
在我奶奶的车里不能抽烟
There's no smoking in my grandmother's cab.
好 那么我得去厕所
Well, then I have to go to the bathroom.
少来了
Oh, please.
不行 不可以随便停车 加油的时候你再去
No unscheduled stops. You can go when we stop for gas.
别这样 前面就有一个休息站 我真的得去
There's a rest stop right up there. Come on, I really have to go.
噢 现在我也得去了
Oh, now I have to go.
到了
Here we go.
- 抓好了   - 什么
- Brace yourself.     - What?
好
Okay. Ow.
- 你不去吗   - 不用了 谢谢
- Aren't you gonna go?     - No, thanks.
瑞秋不上公共厕所的
Rachel never pees in public restrooms.
他们老是没有卫生纸
They never have any paper in there.
所以我的规则是 没有卫生纸 就不去厕所
So my rule is, "No tissue, no tushy."
既然大家都要去…
Well, if everybody's going...
不要关门 钥匙在里面
Don't close it. The keys are in there.
噢 千万不要
Oh, no, no, no, no.
- 怎么了   - 我的打火机在里面
- What's going on?     - My lighter's in there.
该死 排气管不够热 不能点烟
Damn. The tailpipe's not hot enough to light this.
别担心 我可以打开 有人有衣架吗
I can open this. Anybody got a coat hanger?
我有
Oh, I do.
噢 不对 我今早穿衣服时 把衣架拿出来了
No, I took it out of my shirt when I put it on this morning.
所以你父母亲如果没有离婚的话
So if your parents hadn't divorced...
你就有办法跟正常人一样回答问题吗
...you'd be able to answer a question like a normal person?
我只是需要金属线把它撬开
Look, I just need a wire something to jimmy it.
你们其中一个人把胸罩的钢圈给我
One of you give me your bra underwire.
- 什么   - 什么
What?
快点 谁的胸部最大
Come on. Who has the biggest boobs?
胸部最大的人胸罩最大 钢圈也最长
Whoever has the biggest boobs, has the biggest bra and wire.
- 才不要   - 胸罩很贵
- No.     - It's too expensive.
要回车里 就需要钢圈
To get back in the car, we need that wire.
你们自己做决定
Your call.
好吧 摩妮卡的最大
Monica's are the biggest.
这些小红豆 拜托 瑞秋的最大
These tiny little non-breasts? Please. It's gotta be Rachel.
不对 我的是骗人的
No, mine are deceptively small.
我有时候会在胸罩上塞东西
I mean, I actually sometimes stuff my bra.
对 但是你的胸罩还是一样很大
Well, then your bra would still be big.
不对 我是塞在胸罩外面
No, I stuff outside the bra.
女士们 你们就让步吧
Ladies, let's just compromise, okay?
菲比 瑞秋 把摩妮卡的胸罩脱掉
Phoebe, Rachel, take off Monica's bra.
好吧 算了
All right, forget it, never mind.
- 用我的   - 谢谢
- You can have mine.     - Thank you.
钱德 你在干嘛 那里就有一个垃圾筒
Chandler. What are you doing? There's a trash can right there.
我想说只要乱丢垃圾 就可以引来那个印第安人来救我们
I thought if I littered, that crying Indian might come by and save us.
好了
There.
谢了 菲比 你真大方
Thank you, Phoebe. That's very, very generous.
现在来讨论 谁的屁股最正
Now, let's decide who has the nicest ass.
开了
And there you go.
钱德
Chandler.
至少让我吸烟爽一下
Well, at least let me smoke it to the good part.
不会吧
Oh, no.
- 怎么了   - 怎么了
- What's going on?     - What?
这以前有发生过
Yeah, this has happened before.
- 所以你知道该怎么办   - 对 加多点油
- So you know how to fix it?     - Yep. Put more gas in.
嗨 你怎么会来了
Hi. What are you doing here?
我只是在想… 我们分开的时候
I was wondering, when you and I split up...
你是不是拿了录了"风流医生俏护士"最后一集
...did you get the tape that was half the last episode of M.A.S. H...
跟人质回国新闻的那卷带子
...and half the hostages coming home?
但现在是我和苏珊游墨西哥 跟人质回国的新闻
But now it's Susan and me in Mexico and the hostages coming home.
小班呢   -
Where's Ben?
他在睡觉
He's sleeping.
我来得不是时候吗
Is this a bad time?
对 苏珊很快就会到了
Yeah, actually. Susan's gonna be here any minute.
今天是个纪念日
It's kind of an anniversary.
你们不是一月结婚的吗
I thought you guys got married in January.
是另一个纪念日
A different kind of anniversary.
那么…
So anyway...
蜡烛 香槟…
Candles, champagne...
纪念日最棒了…
Yeah, anniversaries are great...
因为爱会流传永世…
...because love lasts forever, you know?
没什么比爱情可靠
There's nothing like it in this life. Money in the bank.
瑞秋和我分手了
So Rachel and I broke up.
天啊 罗斯 我很遗憾
God, Ross, I am so sorry.
你知道吗
You know what?
我很想陪你聊一聊…
I wanna talk about this so much...
但是要找个能长谈的时间
...but when we can really get into it.
- 明天晚餐怎么样     -  太好了
- You free for dinner tomorrow?     - I'd love that.
没错
Me too.
一切都是因为瑞秋找到新工作
I guess it all started when Rachel got this new job.
汽车协会可以来载我们
Triple A can pick us up.
我们靠近哪个城镇
What town are we near?
- 佛里蒙特   - 威斯蒙特
Freemont. Westmont.
威斯伯格
Uh, Westberg?
不知道就别回答
Why are you answering?
我们在哪条路上
Do you know what route we're on?
绝对是27号公路
We are definitely on Route 27.
我们在27号公路的休息站
We are at a rest stop on Route 27...
没有27号公路
There is no Route 27.
- 不是93就是76   - 我不知道
- Either 93 or 76.     - I don't know.
对不起 每次来的时候我都在后座睡觉
I always slept in the back when we drove here.
你可以派人到76号公路检查所有休息站吗
Can you just send someone up and down 76 and check every rest stop?
93号也是
And also 93?
好
Okay.
不行 他们不肯
No, they don't do that.
会有人来救我们的
Somebody will come and save us.
谁啊 过去一个半小时 你有看到车子吗
Who? Have you seen a car in the last hour and a half?
我们应该打给罗斯 或许他可以派辆车来
We should call Ross. Maybe he can get a car to get us.
不行 我不要跟罗斯同车
I am not getting in a car with Ross.
我们只能…
We will just have to...
住在这里
...live here.
- 但是好冷   - 不行
- But it's so cold.     - No.
我不要坐他的车 想其他办法
I won't get in a car with him. Think of something else.
太好了 乔伊和钱德回来了
Joey and Chandler are back.
求救的情况如何
So the going-for-help went well?
老烟枪走到一半就不行了
Smokey Joe here got halfway to the highway and collapsed.
我的肺活量跟两岁小孩一样
I have the lung capacity of a 2-year-old.
那你干嘛还抽烟
Then why are you smoking?
我很不安
It's very unsettling.
对吧 真是太扯了
Right? I mean, it's pretty unbelievable.
他们就这样走了 头也不回的走
They just took off without even looking back.
我才不需要他们 我有你们做我的朋友
I don't need them. I've got you guys now as friends.
你和苏珊
You and Susan.
苏珊会很开心的
Susan will be so pleased.
Seven-one-seven?
717在哪里
Where's 717?
你有帮苏珊留一些 对吧
You have more of these for Susan, right?
没有 但是没关系
No, but that's okay.
我再放点酸黄瓜就行了
I'll just put out pickles or something.
- 罗斯 谢天谢地   - 菲比
- Ross, thank God.     - Pheebs?
你为什么这么小声
Why are you whispering?
我吃了一只虫
I ate a bug.
瑞秋 这里的棉条只要一毛钱
Hey, Rach. The tampons here are only a penny.
我们买回去囤积
Let's stock up.
罗斯 我们车子没油 也不知道身在何处 所以没办法找拖车
We're out of gas and don't know where we are, so we can't get a tow truck.
- 现在需要帮忙啦   - 是的 拜托
- Oh. Now you want a favor?     - Yes, please.
很遗憾你的车子不能动了…
I'm sorry your car broke down, Pheebs...
但是我现在忙着跟我真正的朋友在一起
...but I'm too busy with some of my real friends right now.
但记得让我知道你们安全回到家…
But please call to let me know you got home safely.
菲比 等等
Phoebe, hang on a second.
开我的车去接他们
Take my car. Get your friends.
不 我才不要
No, I won't pick them up.
我们都知道你会去的 因为你不是混蛋
We both know you'll do it because you're not a jerk.
你顶多再骂半小时就会去接他们…
So you can sulk here for half an hour, then go get them...
- 不如一边开车一边骂   - 不要 瑞秋…
...or save time and sulk in the car.     - Rachel doesn't...
我很遗憾瑞秋为了马克甩掉你…
I'm sorry Rachel dumped you for Mark...
你是无辜的受害者
...and you're the innocent victim in this.
但不能因为这样就迁怒你的朋友
But don't punish your friends for what Rachel did.
你说得没错
Yeah, you're right.
菲比 等等 罗斯有话要说
Phoebe, hang on. Ross wants to say something.
- 什么   - 你跟其他人上床
What? You slept with someone else?
我们当时是分手状态
We were on a break.
我们…嗯
We were... Yeah.
你们在哪 我去找你们
Where are you? I'll find you.
你跟其他女人上床
You slept with another woman?
你还有资格说啊
Oh, you're one to talk.
好了
Okay, done.
什么是"命救"
What's "pleh"?
是救命反过来写…
That's "help" spelled backwards...
直升机在天空飞的时候 才看得懂
...so that the helicopters can read it from the air.
蠢人 反过来写是什么
Ha. What's "dufus" spelled backwards?
有车了
Car. Car.
噢 罗斯出来兜风了
Oh, it's Ross on one of his drives.
他来这里干什么
What is he doing here?
他是来救你们大家一命的
He is saving your butt.
除非我惹到某人…
Unless I'm stepping on some toes here...
那我可以闪人
...in which case, I could just mosey on.
州际公路上有很多人需要帮助
I have plenty of people to help on the interstate.
- 别这样   - 我们需要你的帮忙 拜托你
- Come on.     - We need your help, please.
好啦…
Fine. Fine.
完了 别人会看不懂
Oh, no. Now it's not gonna make any sense.
各位…
You guys...
罗斯怎么办 他大老远开来这里
...what do we do about Ross? He drove all the way up here.
叫他回去 我们留在这里滑雪吗
Just send him back, then we'll go skiing?
真是烦死了
This is horrible. It's just horrible.
嘿 我们是不是应该叫罗斯一起来
Should we ask Ross to come along?
但是瑞秋怎么办 要怎么问她
But what about Rachel? How are we gonna even ask her?
问我什么
Ask me what?
可以让罗斯留下来滑雪吗
If, uh, it might be okay if Ross came skiing?
我没有要问啊
No, I wasn't gonna ask that.
实在太扯了 当然不行
You guys are unbelievable. No, he cannot come.
- 什么   - 烦死了
- Excuse me?     - It's horrible.
拜托 我不能去你的神奇小屋吗
Oh, please? Can't I come to your special, magical cabin?
你为什么会想要来呢 你滑雪糟透了
Why would you even want to come? You're a horrible skier.
攻击我的痛处 滑雪技巧
Oh. Hitting me where it hurts. My ski skills.
又来了
Here we go again.
我受不了了
I can't handle this, you guys.
我可以 我的绰号是"受得了"
I can handle it. "Handle" is my middle name.
去头去尾后 就是"受得了"
Actually, it's the middle part of my first name.
好了 菲比 你的车好了
All right, Pheebs, your cab's ready.
走吧
Let's go.
不客气
You're welcome.
抱歉 你是在跟我说话还是跟别人睡觉
I'm sorry. Were you speaking to me, or sleeping with someone else?
我们当时是分手状态
We were on a break.
你干嘛不把那句话录在答录机上
Why don't you just put that on your answering machine?
本来就是 我不是唯一一个同意的人
It's valid, and I'm not the only one who thinks so.
摩妮卡也同意
Monica agrees with me.
什么
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
你昨晚是这么说的
You said it last night.
我是说我能了解
What I said was that I understood.
- 是乔伊同意你说的话     -  好
Joey is the one who agreed with you.
真的吗 乔伊
Really, Joey?
什么
What?
其实没有谁对谁错
You know what? There is no right or wrong here.
不 我认为错的人很明显
I think it's very obvious who's wrong here.
乔伊很明显不这么认为
Obviously not to Joey.
什么
What?
- 乔伊和摩妮卡的想法跟我一样   - 你只会装无辜
- Joey and Monica feel like I do.     - You and this innocent act.
猜猜我是谁
Hey, guess who I am?
看看你们对钱德做了什么好事
Look what you're doing to Chandler.
听着 我们都知道你们两个很难受
Look. We know that this is really, really hard for you guys.
你们不用彼此相爱
You don't have to love each other.
现在甚至不用喜欢彼此
You don't even have to like each other much right now.
但你们必须想个办法和平相处
But please find a way to be around each other.
别让我们左右为难
And not put us in the middle.
否则我们以后就没办法在一起了
Otherwise, I mean, that's just it for us hanging out together.
你们真的想这样吗
Is that what you want?
讲理一点好吗
Can you be civil?
- 好   - 我可以
- Yeah.     - I can.
很好 回车上去 快冷死了…
Good, let's get back in the car. It's freezing...
而且我的胸部没有东西支撑
...and my chest is unsupported.
等等
Wait a second.
那现在是怎样 谁跟谁一起走
I mean, what are we doing? Who's going with who?
听着 你们去吧
Look, you guys should go.
你们都计划好了…
You know, you planned this all out...
我不想毁了你们的周末 去吧
...and I don't wanna ruin it. So just go.
别这样 你开了那么久的车过来
You drove all the way up here.
反正我车子也得开回去
I've gotta take the car back anyway.
明天一整天都得陪小班
I'm spending all day tomorrow with Ben.
没关系的 去吧 不需要有罪恶感 真的
It's fine, okay? Just go. No guilt, I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们回去以后再打给你
We'll call you when we get back.
我们可以去看电影什么的
Maybe we can, like, go to a movie or something.
或是马术表演
Or the rodeo.
那太好了
- That would be great.     - Okay.
我刚刚是在演"海神号遇险记"的 莎丽•温德丝
I was being Shelley Winters from The Poseidon Adventure.
我知道
I know.
再见
Bye.
- 罗斯   - 对不起 我这么晚来
- Ross.     - Hi. Sorry I'm late.
- 你刚刚在睡觉吗   -没有
- Were you sleeping?     - Uh, no.
太好了
Oh, great.
我去帮你买电池 买了最好的那种
I had to get you a new battery. I got the best I could.
这种东西不能省
You don't want to skimp there.
你太棒了
You're a genius.
总共花了112块
It came to about $112.
不过随便啦 给我110就好
But what the hell, call it an even 110?
我明天再付钱给你 再见
I'll pay you tomorrow. Bye.
他们都走了
So they, uh, all took off.
看他们离开还蛮难受的
It was pretty hard watching them go, you know?
好吧 再见
Yeah, okay. Bye.
那我走了
So I'm gonna take off then.